Shubham Jethwa

52, Nilkanth Society, Himmatnagar, Gujarat 383001 * +91- 7878 86 8668 * shubhamjethwa@gmail.com

Career Objective

A workaholic, enthusiast and motivated software engineer with 1+ year of experience who can add value by taking up modern day business challenges and solving them. Possesses excellent interpersonal skills and high interest in working on cutting edge technologies.

Core Competencies

- Java
- C
- C++
- Junit

- Redis
- Maven
- Elastic Search
- Cassandra

Professional Experience

Software Engineer, Evive Health

Bengaluru, Karnataka June 2016 – Present

Working on various projects catering to online medical aid and healthcare analytics using big data and personalized health recommendations.

Accomplishments:

- Gamification of user benefits
- Weight tracking platform for customers
- ETL performance tuning

Programmer Trainee, Evive Health

Bengaluru, Karnataka January 2016 – May 2016

Was involved in business analysis, technical design and development of ETL (Extract, Transform, and Load) procedure to transform the raw medical information into health campaign specific data.

Accomplishments:

- Created 5 ETL procedures
- Optimized the procedures to process records as high as half a million

Projects

Health Data Accumulator

Developed an application to fetch enriched fitness data from device like Fitbit tracker, to make better health and fitness related personalized recommendations. The project involved using Oauth 2.0 for user authentication and was made using APIs exposed by the fitness device.

Angry Birds Bot

Created an artificially intelligent bot that can play angry birds game without human intervention. Heuristic engine created using regression analysis can find the point which causes maximum destruction depending upon the type of structure and bird and hit there. The artificially intelligent bot was programmed to finish maximum levels of the game with maximum possible score.

Know Your Enemy: Compromising Adversaries in Protocol Analysis

As a part of research internship in the area of cryptology and cryptanalysis, I analyzed different protocols based on compromising capabilities of adversaries and created protocol hierarchy from the derived results.

Education

Dhirubhai Ambani Institute of Information and Communication Technology

B.Tech in Information and Communication technology, 2016

- CPI: 7.65/10
- Member of Sports Committee, DA-IICT for academic year 2013-14
- Represented college volleyball team at Shaurya '13, IIM-Ahmedabad
- Coordinator of Synapse '14, annual cultural festival at DA-IICT

Areas of Interest

- Data Structures and Algorithms
- Artificial Intelligence
- Cryptography
- Network Security

Achievements

- Second position in Volleyball at Shaurya '13, IIM Ahmedabad
- Secured first position in Volleyball at KVS Regional Meet (Ahmedabad Region)
- Vice Sports Captain for Kendriya Vidyalaya, Himmatnagar

Interests and Hobbies

- Football
- Vollevball
- Online Gaming
- Travelling